Robert S. McNamara Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: Subject File, 1960-2003 (Box I:77-104)
  - Defense department
    - Post-defense issues
      - Legal cases
        - Westmoreland v. CBS, Inc.
          - Correspondence and memoranda, 1982-1984
          - Court records
            - Affidavit, 1983
            - Briefs
              - Defendant's filings to dismiss and for summary judgment, 1984
                - Memorandum in support of
                - Appendix A (Box I:91)
                - Reply to plaintiff's memorandum in opposition to CBS's motion to dismiss and for summary judgment
              - Plaintiff's filings in opposition to defendant's motion to dismiss and for summary judgment, 1984
                - Memorandum of law
                - Appendix A
                - Plaintiff's counter-statement and appendix B
            - Depositions (Box I:92)
              - Helms, Richard, videotaping of deposition, 1984
              - McNamara, Robert S., 1984
                - Extracts and notes
                - Transcript
            - Exhibits
              - Joint exhibit no. 955, memorandum for the president (1967), 1984
              - Plaintiff's exhibits
                - No. 23-A, telephone interview with George Crile (1981), 1983-1984
                - No. 215, press clipping (1983), 1984
            - Opinions, 1984
            - Transcript of testimony, 1984-1985
          - Notes, 1984 (Box I:93)
          - Press clippings, 1983-1985
      - Official portrait, 1975-1978
      - Pentagon Papers, 1969-1972, 1989, 2001 See also Classified
  - Economy and world trade
    - Domestic economy
      - Budget deficits, 1984-1985
      - General, 1984-1987, (5 folders)
      - Trade deficits, 1985
    - Europe, 1985 (Box I:94)
    - Global economy
      - Competitiveness, 1987
      - General, 1983-1987, undated, (5 folders)
    - Interdependence, 1984-1987
    - Third World, 1984
    - World monetary system, 1984
  - Editors, 1989
  - Environment
    - Research papers, 1985-1988
    - Speth, James Gustave, 1984-1989 (Box I:95)
  - Ford Motor Co., Automatic Radio Manufacturing Co. lawsuit, 1970
  - Foreign policy, 1984-1986
  - Geopolitical file
    - Africa
      - General, 1984-1992, 1998, (2 folders)
      - South Africa
        - General, 1985-1986, (3 folders)
        - Medical Education for South African Blacks, 1988 (Box I:96)
      - Sub-Saharan region
        - AIDS, 1997
        - Agriculture, 1992-1999, (3 folders)
        - General, 1993-1994
        - Satellite Image Mapping Feasibility Study, 1989-1990, 1999, (2 folders)
      - Trips
        - 1982, Sept.-Oct.
        - 1985, July (Box I:97)
          - Briefing book, 1985
          - Miscellany, 1984-1985, (2 folders)
      - World Bank reports
        - Agriculture, 1992
        - Status reports, 1990, (2 folders)
        - Strategy reports, 1981-1986 (Box I:98)
    - Asia, 1993
    - Bosnia, 1993
    - China
      - General, 1986-1997, 2003, (5 folders)
      - Trip, 1982
        - Background material
          - Miscellaneous, 1978-1982
          - World Bank memoranda, 1980-1982 (Box I:99)
        - Briefing book, 1981
        - General, 1982
    - Haiti, election observer mission, 1990
    - India, 1998
    - Japan, 1985-1987, 1993-1998, undated, (2 folders)
    - Kosovo, 1998
    - Latin America
      - Debt crisis, 1985-1986
      - Memoranda prepared for the Inter-American Dialogue Executive Committee, 1986
    - Mexico, 1984-1986
    - Middle East, undated (Box I:100)
    - Nicaragua, 1984
    - Russia
      - General, 1986-1987, 1995-2001
      - Trips, 1988, Mar. 14
    - Soviet Union See same container, Russia
  - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 1983-1989
  - Human rights, 1986
  - Institute for International Economics See Container I:1, Bergsten, C. Fred
  - International development
    - Development strategies, 1985
    - Foreign debt, printed matter, 1984-1985
      - Indexed, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Box I:101)
    - Miscellany, 1990-1991
    - Twenty-fifth inaugural anniversary, 1988
  - Kennedy family
    - Correspondence, 1982-1988
    - Press clippings, 1988
    - Robert F. Kennedy Memorial Foundation, administrative and operational book, 1968-1973, (2 folders)
  - Military Spending Working Group
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995
    - Reading list, 1991-1995
  - Nicholas deB. Katzenbach Chair, Yale Law School, New Haven, Conn., 1985 (Box I:102)
  - Office of National Drug Control Policy, 1998-1999
  - Onchocerciasis (river blindness), 1991-1995
  - Politics, 1986-1987
  - Population, printed matter
    - Indexed, 1980-1987
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-1992, 1998, (3 folders)
  - Post-Cold War and security, 1990-1993
  - Presidential administrations and campaigns
    - Administrations
      - Clinton administration, 1992-1993
      - Johnson administration, wage/price guideposts, 1964-1966, 1979
      - Reagan administration, Reunión Internacional sobre Cooperación y Desarrollo (Cancún Summit), 1981 (Box I:103)
    - Campaigns, 1988 election, 1986-1987
  - Projects, reports, and studies
    - McLean, Sheila Avrin, “An Assessment for Grantmaking International,” 1982
    - Project 100,000, 1985-1990
    - “The Public, the Soviets, and Nuclear Arms,” a joint project of the Public Agenda Foundation and the Center for Foreign Policy Development, 1986-1992
    - “Shaping the Peace: Postwar United States Policy in the Middle East and the Gulf,” Foreign Policy Institute, Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, Md., 1991
    - Strategic readiness study, Rand Corp., 1988-1989
  - Science
    - Bulletin of Atomic Scientists, 1986-1987
    - Climate change, 1986-1989
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1986-1991
  - Social welfare, 1985
  - Southern Center for International Studies, 1988-1990
  - United Nations
    - Conference on Trade and Development, Independent Group on Financial Flows to Developing Countries (Helmut Schmidt Commission)
      - 1969, 1988-1989, Apr.
      - 1989, May-July (Box I:104)
    - General, 1981-1988, 1998-1999
  - United States-Soviet relations, 1987
  - Vietnam War, 1968, 1979-1980
  - Watergate Affair, 1973
- Part I: Speeches and Writings, 1961-2000 (Box I:104-120)
  Correspondence, drafts and typescripts, notes, background and research material, transcripts, proofs, publication and production material, copyright releases and permissions, blurbs and endorsements, royalty statements, printed matter, and miscellaneous material concerning McNamara's articles, books, commentary, editorials, interviews, radio and television appearances, and speeches as well as speeches and writings by others.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject or type of material.
  - Articles and miscellaneous writings (Box I:104)
    - About McNamara
      - Hendrickson, Paul, “McNamara,” Washington Post, 1984
      - Miscellaneous, 1962, 1985-1989, undated
    - By McNamara
      - Correspondence and drafts, 1983-1993, (2 folders)
      - Printed copies, 1982-1993
      - Titles
        - “Blundering into Disaster: The First Century of the Nuclear Age,” Brookings Review, 1986-1987
        - “Can Civilization Survive Defense in the Nuclear Age?” Challenge, 1986-1987
        - “The Challenges Facing the Continent of Africa,” in Anatoly Gromyko's Brink of the Abyss (unpublished?), 1987-1988 (Box I:105)
        - “Financial Disequilibrium and the World Economy,” Times (London, England), 1981
        - “The First Century of the Nuclear Age: Can We Survive It?” anniversary volume in honor of Helmut Schmidt, 1987-1988
        - “The Military Role of Nuclear Weapons,” 1983
          - Background material and notes
          - Correspondence
          - Drafts, (2 folders)
        - “A New International Order and Its Implications for Arms Reduction,” in Arms Reduction (1995), edited by Lawrence R. Klein, Fu-chen Lo, and Warwick J. McKibbin, 1994
        - “The Nuclear Threat: A Proposal,” New York Review of Books, 1991
        - “On Avoiding the Draft,” Newsweek, 1992
        - “The Population Problem: Time Bomb or Myth,” Foreign Affairs (Box I:106)
          - Correspondence and editorial comments, 1983-1984
          - Drafts, 1984, (3 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1984
        - “The Post-Cold War World and Its Implications for Military Expenditures in the Developing Countries,” 1991
        - “The President's Choice: Star Wars or Arms Control,” with McGeorge Bundy, George F. Kennan, and Gerard C. Smith, Foreign Affairs, 1984
        - “Reducing the Risk of Nuclear War,” with Hans A. Bethe, Atlantic, 1985
        - “To Promote Global Peace, Tie Foreign Aid to Arms Purchases,” Global Viewpoint, 1991 (Box I:107)
        - “A Vision for Our Nation and the World in the Twenty-first Century,” in As if the Future Mattered (1996), edited by Neva R. Goodwin, 1991-1994
  - Blurbs and endorsements, 1988-1991
  - Books
    - Argument without End, 1999
    - Blundering into Disaster
      - Awards
        - Olive Branch Award, 1987
        - Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1987
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987
      - Drafts, foreword, 1987
      - Editing and research
        - Correspondence, 1986
        - Footnote references, 1986
        - Glossary and reference notes, 1986
        - Notes and miscellany, 1986
        - Research assistants (David Halperin and Madalene O'Donnell), 1986 (Box I:108)
      - Foreign editions
        - Dutch edition, 1986-1987
        - German edition, 1987
      - Miscellany, 1986-1987
      - Random House, Pantheon Books, 1986-1988
    - The Essence of Security, 1968
    - In Retrospect, 1995-1996
  - Interviews
    - Bronte, D. Lydia, long careers study, 1989-1992
    - Falk, Peter, interview for television film Losing Control?, 1987
    - Merritt, Jack, Claremont McKenna College, Claremont, Calif., 1983-1987
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1968-1971, 1980-1987
      - 1988-1995 (Box I:109)
    - Office of the Secretary of Defense Historical Office, oral history interviews
      - Correspondence, 1985-1987
      - Transcripts, 1986
    - “A Rethought SDI Can End Our Morally Horrifying Reliance on the Bomb,” Los Angeles Times, editorial interview, 1986
    - Rosenberg, David
      - 1961
      - 1962-1963, 1980-1983 (Box I:110)
    - Rostow, W. W., oral history interview of McNamara for the Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, Austin, Tex., 1975
    - Sackmann, Sonja, interview for Tough Choices, by Warren Pelton, Sonja Sackmann, and Robert Boguslaw, 1986-1987
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M. (1917-2007), oral history interview of McNamara for the John F. Kennedy Library, Boston, Mass., 1964
  - Permissions, 1969, 1984-1991
  - Printed and typescript copies (“statement file”)
    - Indexed
      - 1981-1982
      - 1983-1984 (Box I:111)
    - Unindexed
      - 1984-1985
      - 1986-1987, Sept., (2 folders) (Box I:112)
      - 1987, Oct.-1990, Jan., (2 folders) (Box I:113)
      - 1990, Feb.-1991, (2 folders) (Box I:114)
  - Radio and television appearances
    - British Broadcasting Corp., 1974, 1983-1985, 1992-1993
    - CBS television, 1987
    - Japan Broadcasting Corp. (NHK), 1995
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-1995 (Box I:115)
    - Viewpoint, discussion of The Day After, ABC television
      - Comments and reaction, 1983-1984, (2 folders)
      - General, 1983
  - Speeches, lectures, and symposia
    - Chronological file
      - 1985, Nov. 1, “The Challenges of Sub-Saharan Africa,” Crawford Memorial Lecture, Washington, D.C.
      - 1986
        - Apr. 19, “African Development: Challenges and Opportunities,” United Nations Economic Commission for Africa, Second Jubilee Lecture, Yaounde, Cameroon
          - Background material, 1985-1986
          - General, 1986
        - Oct. 15-16, Sanford lectures, Duke University, Durham, N.C.
          - Correspondence, 1986
          - Drafts and proofs, 1986
          - Miscellany, 1986-1987
        - Nov. 5, Committee for National Security, New York, N.Y. (Box I:116)
        - Nov. 17, Kreisky lecture, Vienna, Austria, 1986-1987
        - Dec. 4, Canadian Centre for Arms Control and Disarmament, Toronto, Canada
      - 1987
        - Jan. 12, Los Angeles World Affairs Council, Los Angeles, Calif., 1986-1987
        - Jan. 15, Bay Surgical Society, Los Angeles, Calif., 1986-1987
        - Jan. 29, Rockefeller University, New York, N.Y., 1986-1987
        - Feb. 16-17, Economic Club of Detroit and Ann Arbor Dinner Club, Detroit and Ann Arbor, Mich., 1986-1987
        - Feb. 19-20, “The First Century of the Nuclear Age,” Amherst College, Amherst, Mass., 1986-1987
        - Mar. 19, “Will the SDI Reduce the Risk of Nuclear War,” Pacific University, Forest Grove, Oreg.
        - Mar. 31, Bridges to Peace, Santa Rosa, Calif.
        - Apr. 14, Moravian College, Bethleham, Pa., 1984-1987
        - June 4, Thirty-Ninth Annual Business Conference, New Brunswick, N.J.
        - June 9, Netherlands Association of International Affairs, Hague, Netherlands
        - Oct.. 6, “The Rise and Fall of America: Myth or Reality?” Atlanta, Ga.
        - Oct. 13, “African Development: Crisis and Challenge,” remarks concerning Babacar Nþdiaye's speech, Harvard University, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Cambridge, Mass.
      - 1989, Sept. 8, “Can We End the Cold War? Should We Try?” Commonwealth Club of California, San Francisco, Calif.
      - 1992, Nov. 20, “The Changing Nature of Global Security and Its Impact on South Asia,” New Delhi, India, 1992-1993 (Box I:117)
      - 1993
        - May 24, “A New International Order and Its Implications for U.S. Foreign and Defense Policy,” Center for East-West Trade Policy, Richard B. Russell symposium, University of Georgia, Athens, Ga., 1992-1993
        - Oct. 21, “A Global Population Policy to Advance Human Development in the 21st Century,” University of Texas at Dallas, Dallas, Tex.
      - 1995, May 30, “Critical Issues in the Post-Cold War World,” Smithsonian Associates, Washington, D.C., 1994-1995
    - Correspondence, 1981-1995
    - Drafts and typescripts
      - 1974, 1982-1991, (3 folders)
      - 1992-2000, (2 folders) (Box I:118)
    - Miscellany, 1973, 1986-1994
    - Printed copies, 1962-1967
  - Writings by others
    - Articles and miscellaneous writings
      - Clearwater, John Murray, “The Birth of Strategic Arms Control during the Johnson Administration,” dissertation, 1994
      - Fuller, Buckminster, “World Game,” 1979
      - McElwaine, Robert, The Titans, play concerning the Cuban Missile Crisis, 1992
      - Miscellaneous, 1970, 1981-1994, (3 folders) (Box I:119)
    - Books
      - Halberstam, David, The Best and the Brightest, reviews, 1972-1973
      - Morris, Stephen, Deficits and the Dollar, draft, 1985
      - Ramsbotham, Oliver, Choices, 1986-1987
      - Shapley, Deborah, Promise and Power
        - Correspondence
          - 1984-1985
          - 1986-1993, (2 folders) (Box I:120)
        - Miscellany, 1978-1982
        - Notes and research material
          - 1961-1968, 1976-1991, (3 folders)
          - Undated
    - Speeches, 1969, 1975, 1983-1990,1997
- Part I: Miscellany, 1965-1998 (Box I:121-132)
  Correspondence, family papers, appointment books, awards, financial and legal papers, press clippings and releases, real estate records, notes, reports, land plans and surveys, recreational and travel records, printed mater, and other items, including condolence letters and memorial tributes on the occasion of the death of McNamara's wife, Margaret.
  - Appointment books (Box I:121)
    - Monthly planners, 1981-1995, (2 folders)
    - Weekly planners
      - 1981-1982, (2 folders)
      - 1983-1985, (3 folders) (Box I:122)
      - 1986-1988, (3 folders) (Box I:123)
      - 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box I:124)
      - 1991-1993, (3 folders) (Box I:125)
      - 1994 (Box I:126)
  - Awards
    - Albert Einstein Peace Prize, 1982
    - Athinai Prize, 1988
    - Freedom from Want Medal, 1983
  - Crank letters, 1983-1985
  - Death threat, Zapata Group, 1976
  - Family papers, 1977, 1984, 1992-1997
  - Financial records
    - Asian Ventures Management, 1990
    - International Enterprises Partners, 1982-1990
    - L. F. Rothschild, Unterberg, Towbin, Inc., 1986
    - Steuben Partners
      - General, 1984-1990
      - Reports and statements, 1985-1990, (2 folders) (Box I:127)
    - Stocks and bonds, 1972-1987
  - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, Washington, D.C.
    - General, 1965-1976
    - Kennedy Center Honors, 1988-1994
  - Luncheon lists, 1969-1979
  - McNamara, Margaret Craig (wife)
    - Death of
      - Condolence letters, 1981
        - A-E, (2 folders)
        - F-Z and unidentified, (7 folders) (Box I:128)
      - Memorial service and contributory remembrances, 1981-1987
    - Margaret McNamara Memorial Fund, 1981-1995 (Box I:129)
    - Presidential Medal of Freedom award
      - Congratulatory letters, 1981
      - General, 1981
    - Reading Is Fundamental, 1981
    - Travis-Cline, Suzan Ruth, interviews concerning Margaret Craig McNamara, 1995-1996
  - Real estate
    - Baca Grande, Crestone, Colo., 1980
    - Martha's Vineyard, Mass.
      - Chilmark
        - Land surveys and lot plans, 1970-1974 See also Oversize, (2 folders)
        - Legal records
          - Closing documents, 1972
          - Dewey, Ballantine, Bushby, Palmer and Wood
            - 1971
            - 1972 (Box I:130)
          - Rackemann, Sawyer and Brewster, 1971-1974
          - Robert S. and Margaret C. McNamara Foundation, 1971-1976
        - Sale of property, 1979
      - Flynn, George D., property, 1979-1981
      - General, 1968-1971, 1988-1991
    - Michigan property, 1967-1969
    - Sierra Orchards, Calif., 1980-1981
    - Snowmass, Aspen, Colo.
      - Aspen Ski Corp.
        - Board of Directors
          - 1970-1977
          - 1978-1981 (Box I:131)
        - Correspondence, 1978, 1989-1990
        - Financial records
          - Long-term projections, 1974-1980, (2 folders)
          - Reports and statements, 1973
      - Aspen Valley Foundation, 1966-1969
      - Aspen Valley Improvement Association, 1967-1968, 1974-1980
      - General, 1967-1984, 1990-1992
  - Recreation and travel
    - Alaskan trip, 1993
    - Grand Canyon, Ariz., 1985-1986
    - Hiking trips
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992
      - Pacific Crest Trail, Cascade Mountains, Oreg., 1988
      - Sierra Nevada, Calif., 1989-1990 (Box I:132)
    - Itineraries, 1992-1994
    - Ski trips, 1990-1995
    - Turkey, sailing trip, 1997-1998
- Part I: Classified, 1968-1992 (Box I:CL 1)
  Correspondence, memoranda, telegrams, policy papers, reports, and related items.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Correspondence (Box I:CL 1)
    - Alphabetical file
      - Johnson, U. Alexis, 1969 (Container I:8)
      - Robinson, Charles W., 1975 (Container I:14)
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1988 (Container I:15)
      - Vance, Cyrus R., 1980 (Container I:18)
  - World Bank
    - Committees
      - Development, 1974 (Container I:22)
    - Conferences and meetings
      - Annual meetings
        - 1970, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1970 (Container I:23)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Container I:24)
    - Mekong Basin Dam Project, 1969 (Container I:30)
    - Office of the President of the World Bank
      - Third-term election, 1977 (Container I:31)
    - Reports and studies
      - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Container I:34)
    - United States
      - Government attitude toward World Bank, 1971 (Container I:38)
  - Subject File
    - Arms control and nuclear weapons
      - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks (SALT II), 1972 (Container I:79)
      - Strategic Defense Initiative (“Star Wars”)
        - Office of Technology Assessment Advisory Panel, 1985 (Container I:80)
    - Conferences and meetings
      - 1992
        - May 14-16, Commemoration Ceremony of the Twentieth Anniversary of the Reversion of Okinawa, symposium, Tokyo, Japan (Container I:84)
    - Defense department
      - Post-defense issues
        - Pentagon Papers, 1969 (Container I:93)
- Part I: Oversize, 1973-1974 (Box I:OV 1)
  Real estate land surveys and lot plans.
  - Miscellany (Box I:OV 1)
    - Real estate
      - Martha's Vineyard, Mass.
        - Chilmark
          - Land surveys and lot plans, 1973-1974 (Container I:129)
- Part II: World Bank, 1967-2005 (Box II:1-5)
  Correspondence, memoranda, cables, minutes of meetings, reports and studies, policy and research papers, notes, working papers, financial records, statements, press releases, printed matter, and miscellaneous material relating to the operations and policies of the World Bank.
  - Archives, 2003-2005 (Box II: 1)
  - Bretton Woods Commission, 1992-1994
  - Correspondence, 1969, 1994-1999, 2005
  - Economics department, working papers, 1968
  - History projects
    - Oral history program, 1994
    - Reports, 1994-1996, (2 folders)
  - Memoranda for the record
    - 1968-1971
    - 1972-1981, (7 folders) (Box II: 2)
  - Minutes of meetings
    - Executive Committee, 1981
    - President's Council
      - 1968-1969
      - 1970-1981, (9 folders) (Box II: 3)
  - Miscellany, 1968-1972, 1984-2003 (Box II: 4)
  - Notes
    - Conversations, 1968-1977
    - Field visits, 1974-1981
  - Office of the President of the World Bank
    - General, 1967-1972, 1978-1980
    - Third-term election, 1977-1978
  - Population control, 1967-1969, (2 folders)
  - Retirement
    - Farewell letters and statements
      - 1980-1981, June
      - 1981, July-Nov., (2 folders) (Box II: 5)
    - Pension benefits program, 1985-1998, 2004
  - Robert S. McNamara collection (Joint Bank-Fund Library), 1984
  - Robert S. McNamara Fellowships Program
    - General, 1988-1991, 1997-1998
    - Reports
      - Annual, 1992-1998
      - Tenth anniversary, 1992
  - Seminars, 1982, 1996
  - Sustainable development, 1991-1992
- Part II: Organizations, 1969-2006 (Box II:5-36)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports and studies, policy and research papers, organizational records, notes, drafts and typescripts, agenda and records of meetings, transcripts, project proposals, briefing books, financial records, statements, speeches and writings, working papers, itineraries, press releases, printed matter, and miscellaneous material concerning McNamara's service on the boards and advisory councils of various private corporations and nongovernmental institutions.
  - African Development Bank, Committee of Nine, 1987-1988 (Box II:5)
  - Africare, 2000-2005 (Box II: 6)
  - American Committee on East-West Accord, meeting, Moscow, Russia, 1985
  - Arms Control Association, 1983-2005, (2 folders)
  - Arts West Aspen, 1981-1987, (2 folders)
  - Aspen Institute
    - Conferences and meetings
      - 1983, May 18, “East-West Relations,” notes
      - 1984, Mar. 30-Apr. 1, “East-West Relations,” Wye Plantation, Queenstown, Md.
      - 1987, Aug. 16-21, “Rethinking the Role of Nuclear Weapons in U.S. National Strategy,” Aspen, Colo.
      - 1993, Aug. 13-15, Distinguished Fellows meeting, Aspen, Colo.
      - 1995, Aug. 19-23, “The Future of the World Economy,” Aspen, Colo. (Box II: 7)
        - Background book
        - General
      - 1996
        - Apr. 26-28, Board of Trustees, Wye River Conference Centers, Queenstown, Md.
        - Aug. 1-3, Board of Trustees, Colo.
        - Aug. 17-21, “Change and Prosperity,” Aspen, Colo.
      - 1997
        - Apr. 27, Board of Trustees, Wye River Conference Centers, Queenstown, Md.
        - Aug. 1-2, Board of Trustees, Aspen, Colo.
        - Aug. 13-16, “Change and Prosperity,” Aspen, Colo.
      - 2005, Aug. 4-6, Board of Trustees, Aspen, Colo.
    - Correspondence
      - 1981-1996
      - 1997-2005 (Box II: 8)
    - Governance in World Economy project, 1981-1996
    - Miscellany, 1984-1996
  - Aspen Music Festival and School, Aspen, Colo., 1984-1985, 1991-1999
  - Atlanta Project, 1993-1994